《行尸走肉》
抱歉我迟到了 又停电了
Sorry I'm late. The power's out again.
为什么你一大早叫我来
How is it that you called this extremely early morning meeting,
带早餐的却是我？
yet I'm the one bringing breakfast?
因为你是个好人吗？
Because you're a good guy?
事实似乎如此
The evidence seems to go in that direction.
怎么了？
What's up?
我们以后能每天早上见面吗？
Can we start meeting in the mornings?
好让我给你带燕麦粥
So I can bring you steel- cut oatmeal
问你为什么要见面吗？
and ask you why we're meeting?
好让你教我如何建东西
So you can teach me how to build things.
你想成为建筑师吗？
You want to be an architect?
我想确保那些墙不倒下
I want to make sure those walls stay up.
你觉得它们会倒下吗？
Do you think they could fall?
我觉得可能被撞到
I think they could get knocked in.
可能是多年以后 我跟你一般年纪时
Could be years from now, could be when I'm your age.
你跟我一般年纪时我还会在啊
I'll still be around when you're my age.
但我跟你学点建筑知识也无妨嘛
Well, it wouldn't hurt if I knew some of what you knew.
如何建墙 房子
For the walls, the houses.
新建筑之类的
Some new buildings.
你是想长住？
So you're in it for the long haul?
是啊
Yeah.
你在写什么？
What are you writing?
我喜欢记下一切
Oh, I write everything down.
一切重要的事
Everything of note.
现在该你记了
Now you should.
会有很多要记住的东西
There's gonna be a lot to remember.
这里的一切才刚刚开始
This is the beginning of this place.
你该记下一切
You should record all that.
还有我要教你的一切建筑知识
Along with everything I'm gonna teach you about building things.
- 不用 谢谢 - 拿着吧
- Oh, no, thank you. - Just take it.
- 你必须保护自己 - 我又不用去
- Come on, you got to protect yourself. - Not if I don't go.
我们大老远开车出去
We're not driving all that way
不是为了带着错误的垃圾回来
so we can just drive back with the wrong shit.
是一打这玩意儿
It's a dozen of these.
不管是哪家造的 外形都差不多
They are consistent in appearance across manufacturers.
你们会带对东西的
The shit will be right.
我会安装所谓的垃圾
I will install said shit.
然后电网会重新运转
Then the grid will be fully operational again.
听说你昨晚跟霍莉聊了聊 她是怎么回事？
Heard you talking to Holly last night. What's her story?
为什么要问？
Why do you ask?
- 没什么原因 - 好吧
- No reason. - Mm-hmm.
我就随口一问 别逼我揍你
It's an innocent question. Don't make me hurt you.
一切都带好了吗？
You got everything?
急救箱 黄页
First aid kits, yellow pages.
格伦列出了清单 我发誓我们没问题的
Glenn made a checklist. We're good, I swear.
我知道 我只是喜欢担心
I know. I'm just a worrier.
所以我才建起了那堵围住我们的墙
That's how that wall wound up around us.
爱你
Love you.
保重 爸爸
Take care, Dad.
这话应该我对你说
I'm supposed to be saying that to you.
一切都带上了吗？
That's everything?
- 好吧 - 全好了吗？
- All right. - All set?
你没问题的
You got this.
你总是如此
You always do.
是啊
Yeah.
电网只是个雏形
Power grid was a prototype.
能撑这么久才出问题我已经很意外了
I'm surprised it took this long to start acting up.
我们会让它重新运转的
We'll get it going.
时间不早了 我们走吧
Daylight's burning. Let's go.
我知道我之前说过 但是 谢谢你
I know I said it before, but thank you.
说真的 她是怎么回事啊？
So, seriously, though, what's her story?
真棒 又是一首混音歌
Great, another mix.
现在你要死了
Now you're going die
可以引走行尸
Helps draw them away.
怎么了？
What happened?
我不知道 也许有人不喜欢猫头鹰
I don't know. Maybe somebody doesn't like owls.
- 有人进来搞了破坏吗？- 是啊
- Someone came in here and did this? - Yeah.
这里从没发生过这种事
Stuff like this never happens here.
你有什么敌人吗？
Well, you got any enemies?
你知道有谁厌恶猫头鹰吗？
You know anybody who hates owls?
真遗憾这里没人能调查这种事情
Too bad there isn't somebody who could look into this kind of thing.
我会四处问问的
I'll ask around.
你不必这么做
No, you don't have to.
是啊 我知道
Yeah, I know.
好吧 就算你找出了做这事的人
Okay, so you find the person who did this
又能怎样？
and then what?
会有某种后果
Some kind of consequences.
你听过"破窗理论"吗？
You ever heard about the Broken Window Theory?
归结起来就是 你保持窗户完整无恙
Boils down to this... you keep the windows intact,
就能保持社会稳定无恙
you keep society intact.
这是猫头鹰不是窗户 瑞克
This was an owl, Rick.
是啊 是啊
Yeah. Yeah.
我今天总得干点什么
I got to do something today.
- 那边就是了吗？- 那就是仓库
- That's it there? - That's the warehouse.
看上去从那扇门进出是最快的了
Looks like that door is our fastest way in and out.
首先我们应该查看所有出口
We should know all the exits first.
如果情况有变 就有应变计划了
So there's a plan if things go south.
我们已经有计划了
Already got one.
就是"从前门出来"
It's called Going Out the Front.
诺亚 当心
Noah, heads up.
收到
Got it.
瞧瞧你的准头啊
Look at you with the aim.
格伦说得没错 我们应该检查一下周边
Glenn's right, we should do a perimeter check.
查看出口 以防万一
Know our exits just in case.
我要提前声明 我不该来这里
So you're aware, I'm on record as stating that I should not be here.
你要知道我不会战斗
You well know that I'm not combat ready
甚至没有战斗的意愿
or even for that matter combat inclined.
船到桥头自然直
You never are till you are.
但你得开始出力了 我就是这样做的
But you got to start pulling your weight. You know, I did.
怎么了？
What?
公平地说 我认为我出过力了
All things being equal, I do believe my weight's been pulled.
我把你们带到了华盛顿
I got you all to DC,
以鄙人之见
which, in this man's opinion,
在如今的标准下 我已经救赎了自己
is damn near nirvana by current standards.
但是你没带我们来
Except you didn't get us here.
是我们把你带来了
We got you here.
但假如不是我
But were it not for me
提到这座城市有安家的潜力
and my mention of this city's potential for home and hearth,
你们中没有一个人有远见来这里
not a one of you would have had the vision to come here,
更别提有胆量历尽千辛万苦了
let alone the cojones to travail such a fraught and punishing pilgrimage.
那可是事实 妹妹
And that, sister, is a fact.
冷冰冰的事实
That's as cold and hard as they come.
天 你真这么孬种吗？
God, you're really that much of a coward?
是的 我就是 我说过我是了
Yes, I am. I told you I was.
你刚刚准头不错啊
It was good aim back there.
打靶练习挺管用的
Target practice helped.
其实上周我差点就拿艾登当靶子练了
Actually, last week, I was pretty close to practicing on Aiden.
我也是 伙计
Me, too, man.
我们不能从前门出去
We're not getting out the front.
再等一等
Give it another second.
这地方很大
It's a big place.
里面可能有行尸
There could be some inside.
就算里面有吧
So let's say they are.
我们行动 注意安全就好
Let's move. Let's be safe.
好的
All right.
好了 走吧
Okay, let's move.
- 塔拉 - 怎么了？
- Tara. - Yeah?
- 你没问题吧？- 这条道交给我了
- You got it? - I got this aisle.
它们被某物困住了
They're stuck behind something.
你怎么知道？
How do you know?
我不知道
I don't.
但它们不在这里
But they aren't here.
好了 走吧
All right. Hey, let's go.
当心
Eyes up.
- 安全 - 安全
- Clear. - Clear.
你真有经验
You know your stuff.
我们在外漂泊了很久
We were out there a long time.
可能还有更多行尸
There could be more.
我们开工吧
Let's get to work.
该你了
You're up.
是这个
This one here.
- 没错 - 我们找到了
- Yeah. - We found them.
- 又一个 - 好样的 尤金
- Here's another. - All right, Eugene.
它穿着防弹衣呢 让它走近点
It's got armor. Let it come closer.
我来
I got it.
艾登 住手
Aiden, stop!
住手
Stop!
天呐
Oh, God.
他死了
He's dead.
诺亚？塔拉？尤金？
Noah? Tara? Eugene?
- 你没事吧？ - 没事
- You good? - Yeah.
笼子开了 行尸出来了
Cage is open. They're getting out.
- 我们得去找… - 这里
- We need to find... - Here.
这里
Over here.
她还有呼吸吗？尤金
Is she breathing? Eugene!
离得太远 我不知道
I... I can't tell from right here.
它们越来越近了
They're getting close.
有行尸
Walker.
尤金 你干掉它
Eugene, it's yours. Take it out.
去那个办公室 我去救塔拉 快
Get to that office. I'll get Tara. Go!
你在这里干什么？
What are you doing here?
我没跟别人提枪的事
I didn't tell anybody about the guns.
- 我发誓 - 回答我的问题
- I swear to God. - Answer my question.
你还有饼干吗？
Do you have any more cookies?
派对上你做的那些饼干？
The ones you made for the party?
都没了 赶快走 回家去
They're gone. Now go. Go home.
我家没电
My house doesn't have power.
我本来要去给猫头鹰雕像上色的
I was going to paint my owl statue,
但是有人把它打碎了
but somebody broke it.
这都是无关紧要的小事 山姆
None of these are problems, Sam.
我不在乎你家怎么样
I don't care about your house.
对你的雕像也不感兴趣
I don't care about your statue.
出去
Get out.
- 你能再做些饼干吗？- 不能
- Can you make more cookies? - No.
- 为什么不能？- 因为我不想
- Why not? - Because I don't want to.
你可以教我怎么做吗
Maybe if you showed me how to make them,
我可以自己做
I....I could do it myself.
你想要吃饼干？
You want cookies?
那好 你得去奥利维亚那里偷巧克力
All right. You're gonna have to steal the chocolate from Olivia.
你还要多给我偷一块
And then you're gonna get an extra bar for me.
如果你被抓到了 把我供出来
And if you get caught or you say anything,
我肯定对你不客气
you're not gonna like what happens to you.
走吧
Now go.
- 她怎么样了？- 她的头部受到重创
- How's she doing? - She has serious head trauma.
- 失血过快 - 怎么才能止血？
- She's losing blood fast. - How do we stop it?
急救箱在艾登的背包里 已经被炸了
Med kit was in Aiden's pack. It got blown to hell.
货车里还有一个
There's another one in the van.
她快不行了 我们得抬她过去
She's on her way out. We need to get her there.
好的 我们抬她过去
All right, we'll get her there.
救命 来人啊
Help! Somebody!
天呐
Jesus.
- 他还活着吗？- 我检查了 我以为…
- He's alive? - I checked him. I... I thought...
- 我们得去救他 - 天呐
- We've got to get him. - Oh, Jesus.
最少要三个人才能救下他
It's gonna take at least three of us.
我们有那么多时间吗？
We got that kind of time?
就算把艾登拉下来 他也可能伤重而死
We pull Aiden off there, we could kill him.
难道你想扔下他吗？
So you're saying we leave him?
快去救他
Go, save him.
她会挺下来的 我知道她会的
She'd do it. I know she would.
我留下陪她 保护她 我保证
I'll stay with her. I'll keep her safe, I assure you.
我会的
I will.
好的 我们击退它们
All right, we'll knock them back.
- 你还有信号弹吗？- 有
- You still have that flare? - Yeah.
你朝那边的架子打信号弹
You fire the flare over the shelves.
一部分行尸会被吸引过去
That'll draw some of them over.
好的 剩下的我们徒手杀
All right, we're gonna hit the rest hand to hand.
- 准备好了吗？- 好了
- You ready? - Yeah.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
快
Come on!
(重要建筑即将落成 伍德兰兹购物中心)
托宾真的认为这要花四周吗？
Tobin really think this'll take four weeks?
他是这么说的
That's what he said.
第一次围墙拓张 花了两倍的时间呢
First time they expanded the wall, it took 'em twice that.
你能帮我顶会儿吗？
Hey you...you okay to hang tight?
我得去送份"急件"
I need to send a fax to Cleveland.
大家退到卡车里去
Everybody, back till we're safe in the truck.
弗朗辛怎么办？
What about Francine?
该死
Damn it!
亚伯拉罕
Abraham!
快
Come on.
你先上去
Up and in. You first.
去你妈的
Mother dick.
- 亚伯拉罕 - 当心
- Abraham. - Heads up.
你掩护外围
You take out the ass end.
我对付面前这群丑八怪
I got the uglies in the front.
就这样 排好队
That's it. Single file.
来吧 就这样
There we go. Come on.
别害羞 来吧
Don't be shy. Come on!
去你妈的
Mother dick!
天呐 那家伙还活着呢
Hell, son of a bitch is still alive.
- 你在干什么 - 来吧
- What are you doing? - Come on!
确保他活下去
Making sure he stays that way.
瑞克 我在喝啤酒呢
Hey, Rick, just having a beer.
顺便送你一瓶 感谢你今天帮我老婆
Thought I'd bring you one for helping my wife today.
我不喝 但是很感谢
I'm good, but thanks.
得了 别告诉我你还没下班呢
Come on, don't tell me you're still on duty.
我永远不能放松警惕 你懂的
Kind of always am, you know
迪安娜的派对上除外
Not at Deanna's party.
我看到你了
I saw you.
你在那喝了酒 对吧？
You had some, right?
真希望今天我能多帮些忙
You know, I wish I could have helped out more today.
我四处问了问 但大家没发现什么异常
I asked around, but nobody saor heard anything.
不过是只猫头鹰而已
Well, it was just an owl.
鉴于现在的情况 这不算什么
Grand scheme of things, I think we'll live.
是啊
Yeah.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
听说你妻子不在了
Heard you lost your wife.
你知道
You know...
我知道 看起来好像我们好像没失去过什么
I'm sure it looks like we haven't lost much,
但我们失去过
but we have.
我们失去了一些东西
We've lost things.
我们非常努力地去保住剩下的
Other things we're just fighting like hell to hold on to.
你们经历过那么多事
Everything you people have been through,
不知道你们有没有同感
I don't know if you see that.
我们有
We do.
让你的孩子们来体检吧
Bring your kids in for a checkup.
我知道我让你来过 但他们也该来
I know I offered you one, but they really should come in.
他们在外面有一段时间了 是不是？
They were out there a while, right?
是的 谢谢 皮特
Yeah. Thanks, Pete.
交个朋友吧 伙计
Let's be friends, man.
我们必须做朋友 对吧？
We kind of have to be, right?
是的 没错
Yeah, we do.
所以我们会的
So we will.
回见 瑞克
I'll see you, Rick.
这不是我的错
I take no responsibility for this.
我说过我是什么样的人
I told you what I was.
你应该听进去
You should've listened.
你们所有人都应该听进去
All of you, you should've listened.
没事的 我们会救你出去
It's gonna be okay. We're gonna get you out of here.
好吗？会没事的
All right? Everything's gonna be okay.
你必须保持安静 好吗？能做到吗？
I need you to stay quiet, okay? Can you do that?
好
Okay.
好的
All right.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
信号弹
The flare.
快熄灭了
It's burning out.
快 再来一次
Come on. Come on, again.
- 我们做不到的 - 我们肯定能
- We're not gonna make this. - Hey, yes, we are.
但我需要你的帮助 你可以做到的
But I need your help. You can do this.
尼克 不 不要扔下我
Nick. Nick, don't... don't leave me.
好吧
Okay.
- 好的 好的 - 三
- Okay. Okay. - Three!
你扔下了他们 我们都是
You left them. We both did.
我们就是这样的人
That's who we are.
对不起 对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
它们来了
They're coming.
是我们
Okay, it was... it was us.
之前的其他人…
The others before...
他们没有惊慌 是我们惊慌了
They didn't panic. We did.
是我们
It was us.
不
No.
它们来了
They're here!
你就是这么干的吗？
That how it works with you?
弃他人于不顾 让人等死
You leave people behind to die?
我们有一套规矩 告诉他 弗兰辛
We have a system. Tell him, Francine.
我们有
We have a...
人渣
Asshole.
这么大动静会吸引更多行尸
Hey, all that noise is bound to draw more.
我们今天到此为止 明早再来 好吗？
I say we call it and start fresh in the morning, all right?
去他妈的 弗兰辛 你可以继续吗？
Screw that. Francine, you good?
离天黑至少还有三个小时
Got at least three hours of daylight left.
我需要两个望风的
I want two lookouts.
一个人在铲斗里 一个人在卡车上
One in the bucket and one on the trucks.
如果更多的行尸向我们袭来
Should give us more than enough warning
就能得到足够的预警了
if more are coming after the bash and pop.
拍拍你们屁股上的蜘蛛网 给我动起来
Now pull the cobwebs out of your ass and move.
我们得盖一堵墙
We got a wall to build.
尼古拉斯 站住
Nicholas, stop!
你冲不出去的
Hey! You'll never make it.
当心
Heads up.
我没子弹了
I'm out!
快走吧
Let's go! Come on!
你请辞我们很遗憾 托宾
Sorry to lose you, Tobin.
- 你确定吗？- 我确定
- You sure? - Absolutely.
如果亚伯拉罕听从了我的命令
If Abraham had followed my orders,
她就死定了
she'd be dead.
虽说他因救人而成为英雄
Well, saving someone's life makes them a hero,
但并不意味着他有足够的资质管理施工人员
but it doesn't qualify them to run a construction crew.
他们依然在外面
Well, they're still out there,
整个团队依旧在工作
still working, the whole team.
他带领着他们
And he's leading them.
比我以前强多了
Better than I ever could.
那就这样吧
I guess it's settled, then.
亚伯拉罕回来之后
I'll speak to Abraham
我跟他谈谈 正式任命他
when he's back and make it official.
好的
Yeah.
谢谢你 迪安娜
Thank you, Deanna.
事实是
And the thing is,
我知道你不会后悔的
I know you won't regret it.
他说的没错 你知道吗？
He's right, you know?
亚伯拉罕的能力绝对足以胜任
Abraham's more than qualified.
我让你团队的另一个人手握大权
I put another one of your people in a position of power,
你为他们做担保
you vouch for them.
这已经变成惯例了
It's becoming a pattern.
我们知道自己在做什么
We know what we're doing.
这是你把我们留在这里的原因
It's why you wanted us here.
也是亚伦和达里尔在外面寻找更多的人的原因
It's why Aaron and Daryl are out there looking for more people.
你希望有个未来
You wanted a future.
你需要我们与你共创未来
You need us for that.
说的没错
That's right.
我继续去写耕地计划了
I'll go get back to work on those field plans.
- 我随后就来 - 好的
- I'll be down in a minute. - Okay.
这些烤好后就结束了
After these are done, that's it.
我不会再帮你了 你也不要再来了
I'm not helping you again and you're not coming back.
明白吗？
You got it?
我希望你没想要带走一半多的饼干吧
I hope you're not expecting to leave with more than half of these.
你才干了那么点活
You barely did half the work.
你以前是个好厨师吗？
Were you always a good cook?
山姆 我们不要说话
Sam, we're not talking.
擦台面
Wipe the counter.
你喜欢做菜吗？
Did you like it? Cooking?
以前喜欢吗
You know, before.
山姆
Sam.
我们不必交朋友
We don't have to be friends.
只要不沉默就行
Just doesn't have to be quiet.
我以前很会做菜 那能分散我的注意
I was good at it. It distracted me.
让我忘记我的伤心事
It made me forget when I was sad.
我伤心的时候 会砸东西
Sometimes when I get sad, I break stuff.
什么东西？
What kind of stuff?
你说有人砸了你的猫头鹰雕像
You said somebody broke your owl statue.
是你自己砸的吗？
Did you break it?
为什么？
Why?
你为什么来这里？
Why are you here?
你为什么要偷枪？
Why did you steal the guns?
因为有时你得保护自己
Because sometimes you need to protect yourself.
能给我一把吗？
Can I have a gun?
你为什么想要枪？
Why do you want one?
不是为了我自己
It's not for me.
那是为了谁？
Who's it for?
山姆 是为了谁？
Sam, who's it for?
山姆
Sam.
也许我们可以杀出一条血路
Hey, maybe... maybe we can shoot our way past them.
- 你们还有枪 - 弹药在你那里
- You guys still have guns. - And you have the ammo.
我们得想点办法 伙计
We've got to do something, man.
我们会死在这里的
We're gonna die in here.
一定有别的办法 一定有办法
There has to be another way. There was to be a way.
看这儿
Over here.
来咬我呀 来咬我呀
Come get me. Come get me.
快点 过来
Come on. Come on.
过来咬我
Come and get me.
加油 尤金 就是这样
Come on, Eugene. Yeah.
好了
All right.
我要你们俩 听我说 尼古拉斯
I need you both... hey, Nicholas!
我要你们俩一起稳住门 好吗？
I need you both to keep the door steady, all right?
我来砸玻璃
I'm gonna break the glass.
我们一出去 你就推出去
We get out, you push out.
拿到枪就没事了
We get the rifle and we're good.
好吗？好吗？
All right? All right?
准备好了吗？
Ready?
不 住手 这样不安全
No! No, stop! It's not safe!
- 只能这样 - 不 砸不破的
- This is the only way. - No, it's not gonna break.
会的 我们稳得住 可以的
It will. We can hold it. We can.
相信我好吗？数到三
Trust me, okay? Count of three.
数到三 一 二…
Count of three. One, two...
不
No!
尼古拉斯 尼古拉斯 别这样
Nicholas! Nicholas, don't! Nicholas!
- 该死 尼古拉斯 别这样 - 尼古拉斯
- Damn it, Nicholas, no! - Nicholas!
别这样
Hey, don't do it!
- 不 - 别放手
- No! - Don't let go.
诺亚 诺亚 诺亚
Noah! Noah! Noah!
不
No!
让开 我们得走了
Move over. We're leaving.
回车上去
Get back in the van.
除非你告诉我他们在哪儿
Not until you tell me where they are.
你要么跟我一起回去
Either you come back with me
要么留在这里陪你朋友一起死
or you stay here and you die with your friends.
由你决定
Those are your choices.
帮我把他关到后面
Help me get him in the back.
诺亚在哪？
Where's Noah?
你好 是卡萝尔对吗？
Hi. Carol, right?
对
That's right.
你需要什么吗？
Do you need something?
感觉不适吗？
Not feeling well?
我之前跟山姆在一起 他没事吧？
I was with Sam earlier. Is he okay?
他能有什么事？
Why wouldn't he be?
我能和杰茜谈谈吗？
Can I talk to Jessie?
现在不行
Not a good time.
皮特 不要
Pete, don't.
(一切才刚刚开始)
加百利 怎么了？
Gabriel, what is it?
我要和你谈谈
I need to speak with you.
- 进来吧 - 私下谈
- Come... come in. - Privately.
好的
All right.
撒旦
Satan...
以天使之光伪装自己
he disguises himself as the angel of light.
我担心虚假之光已经进入了墙内
I'm afraid that false light is here inside these walls.
你说你的社区不是天堂
Your community, you say it's not a paradise,
但这里就是天堂
but it is.
能来到这里我很感激 真的
I'm grateful to be here. I am.
但是你让其他人进来是个错误
But you made a mistake letting in the others.
为什么？
How so?
瑞克
Rick...
他的团队
his group...
他们不是好人
they're not good people.
他们做过一些事
They've done things.
他们做过坏透了的事
They've done unspeakable things.
皮特在打杰茜
Pete's hitting Jessie.
或许也打了山姆
Maybe Sam, too.
像他们那样在外面生存那么久
To make it out there as long as they did,
他们必须做一些事
they must have done things.
瑞克自己也说过
Rick said as much.
他们生存了下来
They survived.
所以他们有价值
That's what makes them assets.
你错了
You're wrong.
你不能信任他们
They can't be trusted.
他们很危险
They're dangerous.
你也许以为他们做那些事是身不由己
You may believe that they did what they had to do,
他们很害怕 所以他们…
that they were afraid and so they...
听着
Listen up!
- 总有一天 - 我们今天进展很大
- The day will come... - We made a damn good dent today.
他们会把自己的性命放在你们之前
when they'll put their own lives before yours and everyone else's
然后摧毁你们这里的一切
and they will destroy everything you have here,
摧毁你们努力建立的一切
everything you're working so hard to build.
我建议你们早点睡
I suggest you all call it an early night.
你怎么知道的？
You know this how?
山姆告诉你的吗？
Sam tell you?
他不用说我也知道
He didn't have to.
你为什么现在才告诉我？
Why are you just now coming to me with this?
撒旦
Satan,
以天使之光伪装自己
he disguises himself as the angel of light.
他的仆人是正义的假使徒
His servants are the false apostles of righteousness.
他们不配来这里 他们不配来天堂
They don't deserve this. They don't deserve paradise.
谢谢 加百列
Thank you, Gabriel.
我要好好想想
I have a lot to think about.
我…
I...
我希望自己能早点来找你
I only wish I'd come to you sooner.
我只是…
That I just...
希望不算太迟
I hope it isn't too late.
来人啊 我需要帮助
Help! I need help!
瑞克
Rick.
我知道该怎么处理皮特
I know how this is gonna go with Pete.
只有一种办法
There's only one way it can go.
你必须杀了他
You're gonna have to kill him.